Telephone number: +260 973117632

## **Curriculum Vitae - Leonard N Nshindano**

## **Career statement**

My name is Leonard Nondo Nshindano and I was born on the 8<sup>th</sup> of June, 1985 in Lusaka, Zambia. Since a very young age I have always been fascinated with computers. I was introduced to them in the 3<sup>rd</sup> year of primary school at Simba in Ndola. I have been competent with Microsoft office since Waltheof secondary school and I studied the European computer driving licence while in England. I worked for various organisations in Sheffield, United Kingdom that have added onto my experience. I went onto University in 2013 to study computer science and since then my knowledge of computers has vastly expanded. My graduation is on the 25<sup>th</sup> October, 2019.

## **Work History**

GeldwenCO. (United Kingdom) - 2002 to 2004

Did some general factory work there after completing secondary school. Duties included things like general assembly of goods, packing and distributing of items to other departments.

Blue Arrow Agency (United Kingdom) – 2004 to 2006

Did some agency work with PC world. Duties included answering customer queries on the phone. Booking in computers for health checks. Selling customers computer related items that they've seen online and also referring them to the technical line or the customer complaints line.

Sheffield Hallamshire Hospital (United Kingdom) – 2006 to 2009

Did some administration and clerical jobs with the outpatients section of the hospital. Duties included booking in patients to see doctors, filing patient records, printing letters to be posted to patients. Other roles included answering the phone and basic bookkeeping.

Alishas Internet Café (United Kingdom) – 2012 to 2013

Alishas Internet cafe was my own small business I opened in 2012. My duties there included receiving payments from customers for internet and computer related services. Other duties included supervising customers, installing antiviruses, installing operating systems, troubleshooting and repairing customer computers.

## **Education**

Primary - Simba School - 1991 to 1993

Primary – Chudleigh house School – 1993 to 1997

Seconday – Kitwe boys Secondary School – 1998 to 2001

Secondary – Waltheof school – 2001 to 2002

University – Cavendish University Zambia – 2013 to 2019